<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BounceScrollViewSample</string>
    <string name="introduction_of_house_stark">The leading house of the North, the Starks reigned as Kings in the North until the Targaryen conquest after which they served as the region\'s warden for nearly 300 years. Following the execution of his father, Robb Stark severed ties with King\'s Landing and declared himself King in the North. That bid for independence came to a violent halt when Walder Frey and Roose Bolton murdered Robb and Catelyn Stark at a massacre known as the Red Wedding. In an alliance arranged by Lord Petyr Baelish, Sansa Stark returned to Winterfell and married Ramsay Bolton, who terrorized her. Sansa escaped and reunited with her half-brother Jon Snow. Together, with help from Littlefinger they were able to take back Winterfell, and Jon was proclaimed King in the North.</string>
    <string name="introduction_of_house_lannister">The wealthiest family in Westeros, the Lannisters of Casterly Rock ruled as kings in their realm until the Targaryen dragons conquered the continent. Cersei Lannister\'s marriage to King Robert Baratheon brought the family to King\'s Landing. Cersei Lannister rose to power by eliminating her enemies, though she lost her three children in the process. She now sits on the Iron Throne as the Queen of the Seven Kingdoms.</string>
    <string name="introduction_of_house_targaryen">The Targaryens came from the ancient civilization of Valyria, bringing dragons from the eastern continent and settling on the island of Dragonstone. After a mysterious disaster known as the Doom of Valyria wiped out their homeland and killed most of the world’s dragons, the Targaryens invaded Westeros, becoming the ruling family. Robert’s rebellion eliminated most of the Targaryens and cost them the kingdom. Keenly aware of her birthright, Daenerys Targaryen returned to Westeros after years of exile in Essos. She put her plans to reclaim the Iron Throne on hold to align with Jon Snow against the Army of the Dead.</string>
    <string name="introduction_of_house_baratheon">House Baratheon, founded after the conquest of Aegon Targaryen, has ruled the Seven Kingdoms since Robert seized the Iron Throne from the Mad King Aerys Targaryen. Joffrey Baratheon ruled the kingdom after his father’s death, resolutely convinced of his legitimacy. When Joffrey died, his young brother Tommen became king. After the explosion of the Sept, and Tommen\'s death, Cersei took the throne.</string>
    <string name="title_of_daenerys_targaryen">The title of Daenerys Targaryen:\n“Daenerys of the House Targaryen, the First of Her Name, The Unburnt, Queen of the Andals, the Rhoynar and the First Men, Queen of Meereen, Khaleesi of the Great Grass Sea, Protector of the Realm, Lady Regnant of the Seven Kingdoms, Breaker of Chains and Mother of Dragons.”</string>
    <string name="copyright_announcement">resources come from <u>www.gameofthrones.com</u></string>
</resources>
